Crabgrass.
Red.
Rag. One. Of
my.
Brass.
One.
For
a. While.
He couldn't go on. Could you. Your
injured man let us take you in I
gotta go or I get the Telegraph
that. Will Take You know
pay. A price.
Point.
Home and more.
Home. I
have. Four or.
More or.
Farrakhan's the price I know but the other
talk you know we come our way you can
get the schedule close out the chasm
like this one except smoke one for
a lightweight you know guy who has made
a less than four unit was if it was then
for not prowling around here like this you
got your progress in my office who do you
think you are anyway I can fall down and
I will you can write of I work
at it anyway here let me. Third
trial record. For the last.
Quarter takes on right there
before two thirty but
judge anything. Regarding my name. That's.
Quite evidence.
You're. More or.
Lose. Lose
or are.
The segment seven of.
Them. Not the.
Family not that. Not anyone
I conclude trying on
a possible find out might wake up pick the
wrong way. I would he why on earth with
every going to two stone the
two of us out of whole cloth.
Is quite a man of the gallows a total
lie by many a man with my head in
a woman. What you call my father play
a spy. When
we take you. Think and hope. To have
a black powder bomb on my house. Every
day. I know about the man right now I
can't quite evidence up like
this. I'm worried about
you. And you don't believe. That
only doing good to take my advice is
a pretty far way to miss the corner
thank you very much for your nice nice.
Car ride. At court Evans's
you're not. For heaven
you know him I know quite
a heaven so I hope. On
a quest.
That doesn't flood and I don't know it
will. Never get that bullet out of him
kicking around like that I'm afraid to
give him any more said Jimmy don't read
ahead and that it was a doctor who
can't hear you but the delirious mind
a second for he must be in great pain
not that much laudanum and if he were
reaching for something something
specific I don't understand why now he's
completely inert.
Delirious.
Of the gun in this house the time that
they put these back in the gun barrels.
They will have to get something to tie them
down. Are you all right it's an thing.
That really got the city job with these
wild ones I keep thinking bullets out of
them and setting their bones why they
detonated wind up on both hail no.
God ever speaking about me. Now get
me some more hot water young lady and
I can name up whatever's in store
for him. On how women both.
Mothers Oh tell me again what to do
only about meeting father Harvey
for that of I wasn't out. He was
working on the rest of the new me. He fell
off and I think I'm out of the dust and
tell him Niall he always said I hugged
him before I ever even know his name and
they both know right away though
of course I knew even the people in the
member of the sun and even met with become
a profitable way of life than being
a member of a friend's father had
a beard and is what it
is I think that with
a crash I prefer mankind says
he's got the constitution of
a mountain lion he'll pull through barring
blood poisoning these wild ones never
seem to get blood poisoning common enough
among the godly your so called atheists
always feel so compelled to stretch your
godlessness watching the bullets out
he's in no danger. I think you're
a lot of people know what he did how does
he know that's enough John friend doesn't
speak of such things this
is where I get that man out
of here but he is badly injured this
is uncivilized Pennsylvania this is
a raw frontier you must take
a realistic attitude this is
a place where mayhem theft and murder are
the commonplace instead of the unusual
Well that just the by leaving
a wounded man to die they want your house
by the side of the road and be a friend
a man. Who will believe me I don't mind
you're mocking you've been a good friend
a lot I'm glad I have a logical mind and
a good heart good night doctor. Still
having delirious pals keeps mumbling
about his past. And Freddy's had
a very violent life.
Supper on my bed on the black case.
You know saves lives. Get
real compromise might.
Come out the best. Right your color.
Chart ten in nine. Twenty
nine. Margarine those. At
college are good. I got places
to go on country to put on.
Your alright.
While
a. Violin
that. Put your head on
a rig. For instance.
Where is this. Yellow almost.
Like corn silk. Old Gold.
Colored.
When you drink and have coffee table here
the doctor says he's completely out of
danger just so they think you know Dr Petit
considers him her own personal patient
sit down and we're going to milk the eggs
and when you finish you can go up and
watch him while you carve your world on the
loom he doesn't need watching he had no
temperature these past few
days just to suppress
a delay help the animal restoring his
depleted strength with sleep it's no longer
delirious Of course if you're determined
to watch over him panic happy but take
a pencil and paper with you his first
countries where it should be recorded they
may be of great interest to history I want
possibly the United States marshal who
knows what violence is involved with the
herds frame and his bullet holes when you
don't talk to them and not like you they
said if you know where you can carry this
head in the sand attitude just self I
know we're going to Brianna to let me get
this man out of your house I can dump him
in the establishment that passes for
a hotel in this time dubious community
of ours in that on Saturday I hope that
he'll be off your hands and he's much
better off he sees that who cares what
happens to him we do. I don't think
once when I was studying
medicine in Europe I had
a friend an artist he drew portraits of
people and made them resemble animals they
reminded him of you to draw on this man as
a coiled COBRA. DOCTOR your analogy
terribly imperfect and your naturalism.
Covers don't call out the doctor
was so fond of you and we respect
you so great we are sure that you will
finally realize that religion I'm tempted by
sentimental humanity is really just
a mean hard cold life. That I
stand defeated and furthermore there are
times in this how I feel as if I were
living in
a never never land but don't hesitate
to call on me anytime you need help.
Hello. You're awake. I'm awake.
What is all that. But where
I am I. Don't remember
father and I drove into town.
Oh. The doctor's eyes are they are like oh
this is. You were delirious.
Today. And maybe that's why I'm so.
Little you doing out there. If I could
get through I will not get to talk.
Father you talk
a lot you're delirious. Mother is away all
the progress always hungry is going to
be all right thanks
a lot for housing you know rock smoked
sausage in eggs sounds great doing what you
like three but like six years you'll have
a penny get one of father's shirts and and
a razor I'll get him some food so
I talked
a lot yeah I listen only because I thought
you might say something that would aid
helping you to notifying your wife for
instance when did I say if you had
a wife and I talk about well
you talked of Margaret she has
she fell out of
a dress. What else oh you
mention someone named. Line
that I'll see if you have
a wife we could notify her now why that's
no I haven't been to flattered since Madonna's
won first prize at the Fair back in
Pennsylvania I must be smart in Pennsylvania
some of the members thought it an
exhibition of pride and him I
don't know how I'm going to be in
a little donut unless one eats the many of
them that they could load which is like
they happen to you young men well as the
worst way to check out healthy but the
days no stay and watch creative and I'm
curious to know the effect of think the
exact pound of sausage and twelve donuts
I'll call it in time for the milking
while you people invent something and
talk like that like what the oh well
we're friends. Friends of oh well that's
a side effect many people call this
clicking Oh it's a religion it's
a belief that on the wall and each
human being has an integrity that
can be heard only by the act of that same
human being and not by the I do another
human being that Quaker stuff. I mean
nobody can hurt you but yourself that's
a friend police well suppose
somebody wants you know that with
a branding act or that hurt physically is
calling but in reality it would injure
only the person doing back to four to five
only the door can be heard by me or even
like the very many you Quakers
very few sort of thank you.
The way.
One gentleman wanting kept from my God I
found these out in the road long after I
don't mind going Evans I understand you're
a friend again and I did see the get back
let me know I didn't have to that court
it was the start of it was knocked out
about everything I keep telling him sooner
or later on second thought
you can just tell
me where you as now think I'm on back to
my south where record heavens you mean
where if he ever notice and I'll keep
repeating the question when he's telling
about answering Yeah maybe
if I'd been this gun already
a quick Stalin gentleman I hardly know
Cortef and he lies don't even bring it all
over town what good friends you do I. You
know this but I got many good qualities
and I think that I'm friends I made that
up in my mind I'm asking about court
evidence all I know is the.
Side effect on the story but I can't find
my pet get back in bed always and that's
the only thing that's kept me there that
the doctor says you're to stay in bed for
more than. A group. That's not what you
want to know the person well pass out when
they expect the owlet call me
Mr Which is. That you manifest
a tiresome of power looking for
a test ride in the most elaborate
house even. In my best but
your life doesn't get me my pet
no time well they get my pants.
Whoa what the point was and the cute fat.
Zero zero zero The guy
with the look of. The.
Why good thing on my
passport. Let him work.
The use of thinking to live the
life the year. I was. In my
past what about. Our youth only
the Bhagwan while others with.
A mother to tell them have the wives
and children of. All between lovers of
course. I'm not. But
I'm not I was.
Alright Bowl
the end. Well I knew right away that
night. Was the kind of our life. I could
take a lot of places I go Oh
I'd rather stay here with
a bit of it rather go someplace
else in August I'm like.
Very. Well it's just that. I
didn't like religious people were
quite so bad and then to
write the way I feel and of
a dishonest to say
anything at. All. I used
to wonder why I suppose
every girl. Thought.
About whether. They
are. Well. I wouldn't say
shocked exactly but.
If you get to the point that I didn't.
Know if any I like it just the way you.
Boys did this guy father. Or
that Donald or my father.
When the one of the home
it was a confession
a firearm even up to the one with the power
because you could not provide I could
just. Find. The.
I would only just but then I'd bet and so
do I quite I mean on the other side of my
idea I'll be mad that. I want to come in.
America. You can stand right there
against the light I think we're
you sure run
a ring around me all right you know I don't
think it was right for any of you to
beat me to locating that track after my
boys on the quest I'm willing to let in the
life I don't but I'm
a reasonable man. Read out that's
right the big man the territory
is the biggest man the
territory Loretta So
a lot of people say I hadn't heard
you're nervous no evidence I
can't figure out why you keep stepping on
my toes all the time that you are but I'm
a good loser for like the good of the cause
I like any kind of a loser better than
a winner yeah. You know I had
a chance to do what you think and while
I was following your trail across the
territory I followed by that string and
run out point that you left behind the
wealth around to figure it out this way
quite don't really want that land because
we're again exactly in his line was it in
your line now of course not I was getting
it from that up. And well I figured maybe
you would sell. Your anything jingle
is all right of
a put my hand inside my shirt fine. Five
thousand go there I want twenty
Well OK but I'll have to wait the
thing that's all I got on me I've
got to beat my fucking get it out
now way if the young lady can
find it some of the finest with.
Still are right I was hired by A and. Taken
out that train carry a match is raised
a guy's mind is ill minding
the self won't you. Would you
mind taking this over to Mr Evans please.
Thank you and I'm struggling to save you
up in Iraq. We heard you flat on your
back so I disappointed and you come on over
and get the rest of that money any time
any time I did that you feel able
a feeling of the day when I last so long.
Said love my wife with
a kid draw on my water bag Well I haven't
offended again with something that event
Saturday night this is
a. Time I'd like to tell. All
right. Well you know
quite know what kind of
a boy you think I am you can't do that
with Dan Any wanted human and not for pay
you don't believe in boys so you can't
force me to take it back I'm afraid you're
outwitted darlin I love I've been here
almost three weeks and I had to get going
but you can't you're not you're in no
condition to trap Don't worry York I can get
me grind up and ready
for market I owe them
a ghost. Card
. So I packed my things.
Leaving them. I got
a place in the GO good I wouldn't part
that makes any difference to mummify.
I know some little light. I don't
know could happen to want to know.
About it always the bug.
That as. It is well done
that you feel the love
and the. I'm not the kind of
a guy that does things suddenly. Got
a look before. You can ask anybody they'll
tell you that what happens is on the
dick I just said it.
It's just not for you.
Yeah. Please.
My. Unsaddling.
Got. Up got up.
To something I haven't missed a five and
a big Thank You got them both what is
it but you're right back to school haha
because
a lot of why you don't leave now quit after
this. Guy everybody says is the fastest
man in the territory. Does the.
Sam pretty slow.
And that day's work after breakfast
like that you have to do it then.
Why is the bucket all right because I've
got it I don't know what's happening today
but I think about thank you I don't have
a type one that the first couple doesn't
like very good this morning to have
a good. Lad in the end put water on that
was vegetables this morning the boys work
around he had a big day he wanted to be
a farmer didn't they have
a right. Surely
you can walk to the barn without that
what. All would balance you think one leg
not in the other you know
the right. They are alive.
To have
a custom Hey that's it for
a while as the thing I learned to hate
those things as widely plows and pits
sparked
a fire or. I'll do it and I'll
do it. But that's and I gave him
the well. Now I think just to.
Test the.
Well you want to hate India. Didn't they.
That it took their generation was taught.
Now gotta suck it up you
want. A lot of. Old farts.
To say wasn't played here again it's going
to be all they've flown is needed to
take credit cards and turn the water on
Frederick are. You the man to block the
land just
a dozen friends is going to make you go
then we had done the community day and just
was on his rounds are going to do about it
don't tell me it's right let's go let's
get any water. We didn't
prices why don't we pray for
a fact that Karsten I think turned off
the water and you prayed for him.
Can't you see by committing an
evil act the poor man in just
a little glad there's no wealth because of
the jury gets thirsty around the Arab We
had to wait for
a cartoon I don't watch it funny. And
. Nothing.
Sure you don't leave no second at St
Martin's your how yalla this and the first
pony our saddles each BROCK No matter how
I done it you get mean is there any of
them thank us by is natural born
in that but only neck don't have
a knot either. Get out of the way.
You belong behind
a plow. Of
.
Those guys and get down to take out
a large set of crafts and they
spread that. Are you do you don't
get one of them Frank thanks Dad Yeah what
do you think got the top to play What'd
you say in the top like sixteen inches of
water over there who said I said Oh I do
who might you be when
you're at home Court Avenue
Well anybody might write up here
and say that a court had been
a note around here besides anybody can
say they're him very good there's
a stamp on the saddle OK So the guy gets
to put it he had.
I'm
comfortable and I really
don't want to learn
from that up on the border when I was here
in the good times and I could totally do
if you're dead set on a warning follow
a pedophile it's hard to
get along with everybody
I'm so I think
what I might have. Got
a couple more of them might just I get ten
times as much want to need I don't do
for now well if you never leave him or
make you haven't really got to think so I
think that by some form of.
Well the. World right.
If you're. One of the.
Less Dobbins right now you've got all
water nearly empty right apart I mean you
haven't. Got Do you mind
if I call you quirky
a lot of it was not get out of your market
that the below water all of that that I
have driven over her head and I mean Ford
going to be neighborly or not well I
heard your word that the White Sox.
Puff puff puff was.
That because light image was Oh we always
knew you can go online yesterday I
did thank you Frederick all of us here
in the valley are grateful to it's worth
it's like I was saying and I've gotten
a you throw it extra water why shouldn't I
let my neighbor use it's I believe that
neighbors it's the friendly.
Talk down on your
part. Those words I know Russell that's
a bad first blow the financial condition
of. The man you get down with you know I
don't think you're. Going
to hurt me you know that.
Well looks like your price right now I think
you know thank you thank you John John
said the cash flow says I've done it again
I do feel I didn't feel I gave them more
easily and I thank them for they remember
this great fun not serious man of the
times using the strange
method. For that would be.
I just don't know on a hankering after
a good dress like that. I want to know I'm
going to need that awful good coffee in
the morning thank you want to go home and
shoot my Chinese. You can come back for
more any time you like they're always
playing do you think and I go by good bye
Frederick because I.
Gotta see more of these
neighborhood saying it's wonderful want to
miss it words look you thanks my boy oh
. Excuse me haven't found enough to get
from oh you want to thank me I know I think
now I'd like to talk so not half an hour
of my plunder when I get aboard when you.
Know measures where it's going to keep
me supplied and I want to bring it over
a quarter apiece and then finally come to
understand it with my neighbors because
you know I did all of course you know
I was just scared to death and I'm
a dead beach then people I'm glad you
made me do it makes me feel good
I don't know if I may go.
Then or.
I had dinner going to be
a. Road then again and then just to
go on record as can be taken by with
a blind gig up tried of my get out taken
event Oh I feel real good oh you do know
I'm.
No dress oh it's Thursday you
call it funny part of doing me
a favor he kept the team. And
we do mean other favor go for
a ride with what you're not asking
a surprise plus. I
. Got
a prize for you you know that tells. But
you weren't allowed to work on Sunday
Oh Clark there's nothing I'm not
a Bob Dylan it's just that we don't believe
in doing what we know is wrong and I
make that pretty much detail as I want to
get ready to sell unknowns and sound like
a lot of gents I wouldn't want
to give that much leeway to.
Home.
I. Mean to fight it because. If you have.
To phone in court Evans around here.
Yes I'll get it nevermind I can
do more talking to you. It's been
a long. Three weeks I guess he didn't
then. He didn't disappear for.
Two days during that time did you
know what I've been calling man
that is less from Atlantic the Michael of
the territories I am as I know at that
grain or fully as it currently will
well great. I don't I do but I have one
tall father faced with a gun
held up a bank a stage killed
a couple your right drawing
some say you're afraid ran
but I guess you'll have to take the lady's
word for it when you want to read or
Steve is going to get around to killing one
another all right we want our arses out
of the same trough Well I'm sure we're
looking forward to having the survivor you
know I'm
a figure in Man sometimes I
don't know all the answers like
that fellow Great heavens and a man with
a coat while he was acting as Wyatt Earp
deputy over the phone one day he joins in
his badge and starts bowed himself
a nice cattle spread suddenly
sounds odd and goes on
a prod why that's when I figured you
had sometimes things connect
about that time from
a cough want Ennis went down in front of
the radio Stevens What was reached at the
time and some say the gambler standing
there grabbed his hand maybe that's
connected to Stanley world in this knowing
two things connected I know
a lot of people. I'll
figure it out I really do
I'm patient young lady will be looking
in with your eyes all bugged out
like
a guy words there ain't no
future in it so long folks Great
please stay away from the right as
a thief yells me money no where am I
going out on top and be even more worse
than I be worth of him go down and if I
go down cars don't you see though I be
a guy with him I'd still don't make it
sound so cruel and where'd you see why I
could not see you. I was like up Loretta.
It's better in its way every time he opens
the door every time he hears once that's
coming around the corner all right I'll
start sweating like an ice mate as food
won't set Well I rest of
his life. All right but
if I'm going to be holy I
gotta get some fun out of it.
Or lose.
You know I feel like that the God of the
time the whole week since last June.
Or when.
I was. Almost. A choir.
I thought at least you know Willow hello
that's her name as we're at mess weren't
around
a McCall I don't know how do you do just
fine thank you Well well well you said
that before we don't want
to keep you if you're in
a hurry lemme know I mean I've got no place
to go away have you can you comment on
whether we should like to meeting
so maybe yeah some meeting
you don't want to go do you mean I think
you're good we'd be happy to have any from
the court you would let's just you know
man I sure am an old friend of college I
remember one time we were children cattle
down in the lot already. Thanks stampeded
and what pulled me right out from underneath
them and that was all that I remember
and opals Palace down in San Antonio where
light I know but I was on my side if you
can join in the girl get the others out
of town Thank you Miss Day along with day
my I have my. Old
where. I have good down
rules concerning that with.
One therein is. That if bow would
enter into life keep the coming.
All of them to him. And
God. Our Selves not till
now shalt not. Now sounds not bear
false witness. On and I thought
oh I'm not knocking and I'll shout
not by me but I don't know.
What comes out of that thing that makes
it worth all as work for us in putting up
on our going to flock like
whatever you do about it.
And that was our horse you
are. By the way I got
that maple sugar like so much little excuse
me I'll put it in the bank you know.
OK Isn't this Morgan baby never
mind that you didn't invent
a. Method like his father. Oh.
I'm coming out next week to the worst. Oh.
Well I'll get some water
here let me open it for
a let's think the frozen pony
the
old.
Phone the let's put I
want some of the flower.
Sick or some. I don't believe.
The baby yeah I know. You know
not to talk of course not well I
can't tell the test that but I got something
I think you'd like to hear the radio
station is planning a big play
is going to jump up some guys in
a moment to trail head up no
I think it may be you and me
a couple of friends could sort of play
copycat and you heard me didn't you you're
going to have my part of it. When I listen
to you pass another chance to rest in
the right oh that's right once I'm out
of the old way it's fun. For the day
think in your head and that's back it all
shuts you up you know I don't touch me
lately you know used to
my want to hit. A lot of
a lot of class. Chatter this is.
Become aware.
That I. Have your
attention. When we all know the purpose
of this meeting at three four is always
to give thanks for the goodness bestowed
upon. But also to give thanks for the
particular that the fields are again water
and the crops and the livestock price is
too much for a lot like the
head of the valley. Let's take
a look at it is the third
coming for ten life. Or to have
a. Friend
.
Happy to present you with this
token of our friendship for you.
This is quite evident. For having to have
him here with us because he provided
another resident It reaffirms our belief
that all men are good if they're strong
allies. If persuaded Frederick Carson
to let down the water I join him in
a man who was a friend to other man is
a happy man in South. I
shake your hand.
I want to talk to you
but just not like I'm butting into your
business and I am and you want to give me
a watch with
a gold case for doing it you dimwitted
nail Bender marry that girl marry are sure
you're my intent when she knows how I feel
how would she know stop yammering about
she wanted ours as
that's no way to talk to
a girl to talk to or about her and
marry and do it quick say come
on.
There's no this and then I know you're the
son of Joseph the son of the valiant men
of Pepsi who had done many actions out of
school to men as well as been with down
a slew three lines in the midst of the
prison the time of you know. Free lance and
then a nice little an Egyptian
who had a sword he took
a lawyer still wouldn't seem with
a sense I guess that must mean
a club Well brother this is good writing
Let's go what about the Bible you can fill
in
a way that would be bad not thinking that oh
it's just one book I'm sure going to read
it.
I'd better take it back
to the morgue and. A
fight is quickly so
that's me I don't know.
The. Whole.
Iraq. Yeah right. Apparently.
But Madeleine.
And I had.
Rather.
The rat rat.
The grass.
Hey click when I speak it means. I think I
hear when I get stuck
Why don't I let this book
when. You know you're not
government waste I like it just the same
when I cut your head what's. The what's
next for this life. I'm going to get to
know everybody just to think I was to think
of an interesting way of going and you know
quit I hate the heat. And then I said I
want he wants Montana and I dreamed about
it all the next night and of course
always witnesses and you going to shoot the
witnesses Zog jabbering on let's go to
a degree keep out of it and then you know
a lot more bikes. And I think. It change
your mind about who the writer was what
these guys that up on that hard OK You got
it. And whether you're just crown right
on the turn on in front of a lot of
people going to say we're in for
a big night in town. Eight point zero.
Four or. More or. Go forward.
Or with.
Our Web
site or. One.
Rather
. Rapid
rather
. Where. My
wrath
. At the heart like where
is. The thought is.
And I wish I had the I now. If
you're white I'm a loop would be
a thing around. Oh.
You're.
Another campaign may be
a lot better than what it is you now get
quick action I've gotta tell you I don't
like the. Well you like
I've. Been so I live in.
No time. Where. Maybe just plain bored.
Sad baby you never bored I wish
I had that night. And I've been
a long time to determine
that by hearing one of the.
Remind me of. Tiny.
I'll go live.
In less romantic. A lot more
adult. Like the turn of the
whale when you die of
a fine chance I don't want to farming. At
all when you're trip around the world.
The customers are waiting and
that's no way to treat customers.
I Pod.
All right
Paul
. Of Pi proud mama
read. This Deca blow by point
forward point my
point now thing on your are all I.
Have put my thing out of. My. I
love the way they quote
All never told Paul was.
Point guard for once more. I
post something I've been
looking for blowhards by.
The my lab Lol my I was never
married for more lol I
had my god money the poor. Poor I
had my mare and I may not like the
seven hundred I got to live but not my
for. Her I already got
a ride home and I'm gay I swear to god.
I put my modeling back. I never. Left.
The I. Know I won't.
Loan money to Iraq.
I've been lied to glad. That's money real
money the side you have to come but i
never going to act I didn't
say it you interrupted
a very important discussion on serious
matters regarding big things with my
brothers don't like it Gentleman gentleman
no Probably we just put the place back
together at the last second to the penny.
To break into New York we had many of the
blankets I've had
a dreadful time keeping body and soul
together. But what I think is going to happen
happens around on
a full day. Trip but the
man you have lunch with goes
back about this oh well I don't.
Know strolled around the crowd
some citizens tell me that's good.
Tempered. I mean to go apologize.
Right up.
My what. I can tell in
the aftermath right back
oh.
Well I'm in the flesh. And
I'm not going to make
a movie that. As.
A half an hour later. You know in my
mind that whatever that that I've already.
Been the best out of my bag. As.
The guy was.
Left. Imus is there on less grasp
a minimum. For
the right place how you deal with.
The love of. The. Boy the second
one thousand which we promise.
All right now are those
already. A
sour. Is good
lace. Oh honey I was offering to give her.
Our airfoil I've never
borrowed I when I know I've
narrowed the Iraq I know I'm going to the
Oh it was OK I got money it was
a lovely lady got a bit of
a fight I tell you we really ought to
be thankful for our blessings I haven't
written that Bible like that is something
I never thought I'd know what. I know my
way the Bible. I.
Want. The one to stop
them with what are you going
to be forgotten something.
Tell me what is the deal with the I'm
in the cloak don't belong on the hat
on.
A Well I.
Heard that on my part but
it gets. On the border for
a while of course you're always
welcome Chris. Allowed let
a lot of these mails and that last shot
but not very good the flour you know
allowed the stick around to get one right
up to the top really penny. Help me.
Does it take to defeat a
few chickens mother at
a time. And then. You
can back it. Why.
I don't know exactly why did you go I was
not saying anything I don't know that
exactly. I think it was because I've tried.
I know that sounds strange and I think
that you know what I mean. You were frightening
because I was what you thought that
living with me would be
tiresome and dull after
a while. Try some of the because
I already know the it's
a baby here on the farm of our puppy the
people love Nora and stayed together
forever after. I'd had such
a fool not to know that out right away
I'll be glad when people love that don't
have to follow that they marry say together.
I know that sometimes as I pray I
never going to run I let me talk
a lot of why the body was right I was
around her leg and when you got back to the
route. I might get my God. Whatever
you want so I took it and.
I go away you go it. Go
away they go to. The
war or.
I used to be an engine forever I just
can't help walking up soft on people
one missing young man been doing and
traveling since I was here last well no
because nobody likes to big heard
a few days ago I miss that
country time why after you know
I've been traveling a lot
in a crowd at the L.I.R.R.
Scape that I did just
that and you're covered
a lot of country you're right weary animal
I just want to see with that young lady
life for you I was going to
you've been over Castle Verde way I've
been to Rimrock and I've got witnesses to
probe witnesses for instance Randy McCall
Christine Taylor That's right
career witnesses who else
Lyle and Neil I suppose he'd make
a good alibi witness for you Randy
Christine in Laila There's three to
drive through solo so I
knew that too and it.
The med Jughead gonna
have press jump earlier.
There's
a mist again acquired And I'm patient
that's what hangs on you fellows in the end
I'm.
Glad. To talk about
a man Louis. Or
are. One. Or or
whether or are
poor. Or or
why
or why
or why the or
why
or why. Or why why.
Why or why
horror
when
more
light but I was part. Of our course
where. More.
Why
why. Why.
They decided never thought I'd see
prevents one on the planet when he walks
it's not that you do I taught him
all I figured you to hurt him
except you were thinking to right and then
to get some real important business to
attend to someplace else I'm sure but
I always like to keep track of your
whereabouts
you know quick I always figured on
your new rope and hanging you as
a kind of respected you you never
took the best of things and on the
men went down looking at you mind
your own business usually do
it's the same things don't always
turn out the way they should now that
little gal should marry some young fella
who know what to do with that class
why don't you take up that hard and
move on son your own father raised
a lot of grain cause he gets
it kind of
a fellow that she thought was no where
he was I have to run you off well
now tell you I never have been run
off no place yet claim to stay
but it just so happens I got to be gone
you know quite You don't rate
a new rope with me. There's
a lot of food for our nonsense that to
go with it I'm not going to stand for
a lot at best not then I'm back to jabber
and people looking at me just doesn't get
in their. Clothes. Well
yes or no. Second Blackberry.
Her. Daughter
i Pad.
My. All right
oh I heard
All right. I thought we had an uproar.
And never did like like that right now I
know I was right. Too much work connected
with me I guess my friends.
All. All.
Like out there the wife I know I'm doing
all right. Well it's all right for you to
wives and they both but it might and I don't
trust them to decide to take her side
. And I'm for that my that's not
of the two of us at all at the.
Day that it does or that.
On my list I don't
like the sound of
a clear. But they have to get that you
know. So I have read me get it done and.
It's on the somewhere along with the cat
OK. Folks had been placed like the Indians
and yes it was
a big fella cattlemen one ally Lebanese
younger days I think right now I
wasn't too careful this can't be true
Israel that. Most of the old gentlemen were
like that. Iran. Is quite
a good. Name as well and if it
was down in again lives like.
That I grabbed
a gun I'm just the drill.
That they had. That
what. Well I just danced around
a place like. Quite. Old
. At
the or around. Zero zero.
Zero zero. Zero zero zero to go
I know and it got it got all right I know.
The Red.
Rag.
All right.
Whereas
the as.
Rather
.
Rapid
. War with.
The the.
Well but I. Haven't I guess.
That's trying to pull out.
I don't have to be worried about paying
mother. I can't help worrying about
a channel. Get that up in the quiet of.
The
of. The you.
Think it's amazing the
buried uses to which men put alcohol to
each different individual it's either
a stimulant a depressant and an a
dime just not I'm using it as an
a dime get to the point the practice of
medicine is one of the most infuriating
professions known to man. It takes thirty
years of experience to teach you that in
the final analysis there's nothing to do
but stand and watch
if you had
a lucid moment. Better speak to her. I'm
not trying to argue out of anything
that may be able to stop and think.
She would like this correct I'm not arguing
for or against her point of view but I
know that to her the world's worst
tragedy would be that you should kill
a man of course you could argue logically
that she wouldn't know whether you'd
killed him or not I think he'd know. And
a discussion has to have at least two
protests I'm going to hear if you're to
answer me I'm. Quite.
If I felt cynical it would be
a good opportunity to observe
that we're about to see
a perfect example of an eye for an Eye
Center Unfortunately I can't call
a captain for. I'm too
tired to be cynical I'm.
The guy. But the other gentleman
must not be moving about Mother I
gotta go it may not get back into the
business the new man and I told you to keep
in bed you want to commit suicide you
know the end of those covers young lady.
There's no favor. Of the must do what
the doctor said Mother please you can
understand. I can't understand
a top I must be some logical scientific
explanation I'm too old to start believing
in America rapper in black.
America. All right.
Not to have had the cover. I never let
that Hondo Jeffy pistol whip me. I
don't put out here to Bob. In the middle
to start out of the whole caboodle. My
quest may want to speak well I was not
city several years back when the orcs my
plans were gotten to know me I'm worried.
That I. Dismissed it as.
The old. I'll write of David even
mean to that mom was it. Thank
him
a message. Saying. My
love I didn't write the right. Line
on the driver get excited when
you make
a big one like this one going bad then I
am he went on some Angelos. No I guess.
I haven't found home. I'm just
a carrier Yeah. That the come out
on the Street is waiting for me
was that it. Could have been.
What it is a joke or Devon did take
a look at the streets and
it really isn't. Jack
take
a look in the street that
allow Brian a black cat standing at
a blacksmith's shop mind
if I use
a buy dopey. I
don't like the Caps got nine
lives. Maybe OK it's probably not
he also said he was curious to know how
much what it would take. To build up in or
to come out and to get there is going back
to the better periodontal street if you
want to and somebody has
a back and you drink this
sure I don't have to spend
money and come on I want that shop marches
around town Oh I thought I was out of
town an hour ago that's good but when
I'm around here to spoil it I play
Yeah I bet that's just exactly
how you men think. But.
Rather. One.
Around. Grab the rare
crab
. Grass.
Arrow why why why.
Why why. You're.
Married. You're.
White. Brad red
borer. All right.
Or wrong. Whoa whoa.
Whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa.
All right. Or are.
The OR OR
OR OR. Or or.
One. That might not want to.
My next time around quite. A friend.
Or or Gore are.
Already
. Going to work God right.
I had him dead to rights. They got the
biggest state Still I figured I'd watch the
right as. You down then. I'd hang you son.
Dylan Freeman talks with one
stone so to speak. Another and
Another never works out right.
Or left to get it right. And
I'm making the. Journey
a matter of time and I knew. I
may miss it. And now I know I'm
a farmer. All right.
Last quarter.
I quit my loot that. Only minutes where
you're going to release one what are you
going to do with it. And I'll roll
him over so. With a new rule.